pigtailpals.com 2019-10-16

# Privacy Policy | Pigtail Pals

### **Updated On: October 19, 2019**

##  **Website Disclaimer**

The information contained on this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Pigtailpals and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Pigtailpals. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Pigtailpals takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

##  **Our Privacy Standards**

Pigtailpals (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the website [https://Pigtailpals.com/](https://pigtailpals.com/) (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from [https://Pigtailpals.com/terms/](https://pigtailpals.com/terms/).

##  **Information Collection And Use**

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

###  **Types of Data Collected**

####  **Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  *  _Email address_
  *  _First name and last name_
  *  _Cookies and Usage Data_

###  **Security Logs**

The IP address of visitors, user ID of logged in users, and username of login attempts are conditionally logged to check for malicious activity and to protect the site from specific kinds of attacks. Examples of conditions when logging occurs include login attempts, log out requests, requests for suspicious URLs, changes to site content, and password updates. This information is retained for 60 days.

  *  **Who we share your data with –  **This site is scanned for potential malware and vulnerabilities by Sucuri’s SiteCheck. We do not send personal information to Sucuri; however, Sucuri could find personal information posted publicly (such as in comments) during their scan. For more details, please see [Sucuri’s privacy policy](https://sucuri.net/privacy).
  *  **How long we retain your data –  **Security logs are retained for 60 days.
  *  **Where we send your data –  **This site is part of a network of sites that protect against distributed brute force attacks. To enable this protection, the IP address of visitors attempting to log into the site is shared with a service provided by ithemes.com. For privacy policy details, please see the [iThemes Privacy Policy](https://ithemes.com/privacy-policy).

####  **Usage Data**

We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

####  **Tracking & Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  *  _ **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service._
  *  _ **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings._
  *  _ **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes._

##  **Use of Data**

Pigtailpals.com uses the collected data for various purposes:

  *  _To provide and maintain the Service_
  *  _To notify you about changes to our Service_
  *  _To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so_
  *  _To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service_
  *  _To monitor the usage of the Service_
  *  _To detect, prevent and address technical issues_

##  **Transfer Of Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Pigtailpals.com will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

##  **Disclosure Of Data**

###  **Legal Requirements**

Pigtailpals.com may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  *  _To comply with a legal obligation_
  *  _To protect and defend the rights or property of Pigtailpals.com_
  *  _To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service_
  *  _To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public_
  *  _To protect against legal liability_

##  **Security Of Data**

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##  **Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

###  **Analytics**

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

  *  _ **Clicky Web Analytics:  **Clicky Web Analytics is an analytics service offered by Roxr Software that tracks and reports website traffic. Roxr uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. For more information on the privacy practices of Roxr Software, please visit the Roxr Privacy & Terms web page: <https://clicky.com/terms/privacy>_

  *  _ **Statcounter:  **Statcounter is a web traffic analysis tool. You can read the Privacy Policy for Statcounter here: <https://statcounter.com/about/legal/>_

## **Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

##  **Children’s Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

##  **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

##  **GDPR Compliance**

Pigtailpals follows and complies with all GDPR regulations as it pertains to the [General Data Protection Regulation on Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation).

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the following data protection rights:

– If you wish to  **access, correct, update, or request deletion**  of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us at contact@Pigtailpals.com.

– You can  **object to the processing**  of your personal information,  **restrict the processing**  of your personal information, or  **request portability**  of your information by contacting us at contact@Pigtailpals.com.

– You have the right to  **opt-out of marketing communications**  we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send you.

– If we have collected and/or processed your personal information with your consent, then you can  **withdraw your consent**  at any time.  Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

– You have the  **right to complain to a data protection authority**  about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

##  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

By email: contact @ Pigtailpals (dot) com  
By visiting this page on our website: [https://Pigtailpals.com/contact-us/](https://pigtailpals.com/contact-us/)
